Welcome to MarvelousDesigner's tutorial video on home appliances.
In this tutorial, you will learn some preparations we need to make before creating home appliances.
It will be more convenient to import 3D objects separately before creating home appliances.
Let's import the bed part first as a virtual model.
Then import the rest of the objects one by one.
Make sure to increase the size of the bed part.
After importing all the objects,
save the whole thing.
This will become a project file.
You can download all the OBJ files from the link in the description below this video.
When you import these objects separately, you can adjust their position separately.
After selecting an object, you can use the location tool to adjust its position.
These bed parts are used as a whole OBJ, so they are also together when adjusting the position.
Since it is imported in the form of a virtual model, this object can be hidden or deleted in reverse.
If you hide an object, you can right-click in the 3D window and select Show All Objects.
You can also hide objects in the 3D window and select Show All Objects.
You can also hide objects in the 3D window
In the production of home appliances, you will often use the 2014 Stock Grid button.
These operations are also done via the DC fee tip you submitted.
After editing the virtual model, you can use arguably the true-file olanput function and hence the 산 WTO.
Once you have adjusted the virtual model, you can use the cancelled and touch fixes function.
It is because of the adaptability that the model is inserted into the model, so that there is a conflict with the fabric, so that each object has a default surface diameter of 3 mm.
You can reduce this attribute according to your needs, so that the fabric is more suitable for the object, and vice versa.